<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>LSUS Community Flash Briefing</title>
        <link>https://www.lsus.edu/why-lsus/calendar</link>
        <description>Monthly LSUS campus events update, created as a trial project for MCOM 215.</description>
        <language>en-us</language>

        <item>
            <title>LSUS Community Events: November</title>
            <description>Welcome to the LSUS Community Flash Briefing, a monthly update created as a trial project for MCOM 215! Here’s what’s happening on campus this November. In Week 1, join the Student Organization Council Meeting on Friday, November 1st, at 11 a.m. in the Student Organization Lounge. Then, on Monday, November 4th, experience Hamlet: Piloting a Shakespeare Experience with showings at 11 a.m. and 6 p.m. in the University Center Theater. And remember, Daylight Saving Time ends on Sunday, November 3rd, so don’t forget to set your clocks back! In Week 2, we start with Election Day on November 5th. On November 6th, head to the Health & Wellness Fair in the UC Ballroom from 10 a.m. to noon for wellness tips and resources. November 11th is Veterans Day, and the same day kicks off World Kindness Week with a virtual scavenger hunt at noon, accessible online. In sports, cheer on Men’s Basketball as they take on Nelson (Texas) on November 5th at 6 p.m., and support Women’s Soccer as they face Texas A&M-San Antonio on November 7th at 1 p.m. For Week 3, World Kindness Week continues through November 17th. Later in the week, on November 21st, join us for a basketball doubleheader as both the Women’s and Men’s Basketball teams play Texas College—games start at 5:30 p.m. and 7:30 p.m. Let’s pack the stands and support the Pilots! In Week 4, we celebrate Thankful Monday on November 25th from 11 a.m. to noon, bringing some gratitude to campus just in time for Thanksgiving on November 28th. Finally, on November 26th, don’t miss another exciting basketball doubleheader as our Women’s and Men’s Basketball teams go up against Louisiana Christian at 5:30 p.m. and 7:30 p.m. Thank you for tuning in to this LSUS Community Flash Briefing! Please note, this is a trial project and not an official LSUS account. Stay connected, stay involved, and we’ll see you around campus!</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2024 09:00:00 CST</pubDate>
            <link>https://www.lsus.edu/why-lsus/calendar</link>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
